zeobit.com 2011-12-26

# ZeoBIT

#### Introduction

We, ZeoBIT LLC (the "Company"), are aware about privacy issues that occur during the usage of products, services and websites. Therefore we strictly follow the data protection law of California, United States, regarding your personal information. Our privacy policy applies to:

  * using the Company’s products and services,
  * visiting the [http://www.zeobit.com](http://www.zeobit.com/),
  * visiting the [http://MacKeeper.com](http://mackeeper.com/), [http://MacKeeper.ZeoBIT.com](http://mackeeper.zeobit.com/), [http://PCKeeper.com](http://pckeeper.com/) or [http://PCKeeper.ZeoBIT.com](http://pckeeper.zeobit.com/) websites,
  * visiting any other linked pages or application services offered by the Company.

By doing all of the above actions you confirm that you accept our Privacy Policy.

The following Privacy Policy covers handling of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected by the Company when you use our products and services.

#### Personal Information We Collect

We gather the following data from our customers:

##### Information Provided by You

You will be required to provide your Personal Information at our website or in any other way. This information is:

  * Login and password,
  * Name,
  * Contact details,
  * Payment details etc.

This data enables fast and efficient rendering of our products and services to our customers. In addition, it is used for communication purposes, such as notifying you about product updates or special offers.

##### Information Collected Automatically

In addition to information you enter yourself, we collect technical data such as:

  * IP addresses,
  * Cookies,
  * Browser information.

This data is used for the following purposes:

  * Finding out how many people visit our website and how frequently,
  * Learning how many people use our products and services,
  * Finding out which products and services are used more frequently than others,
  * Collecting some other statistical information.

Automatically gathered data is completely anonymous. Therefore even if it is revealed to some third parties, this won’t affect your privacy.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to track your actions on our website. These small text files are stored on your hard drive and make it possible for our systems to recognize your browser. You can turn off cookies in your browser, but then you won’t have access to some essential features of our website.

#### E-mail Communication

From time to time you will receive newsletters and various promotion materials from the Company notifying you about product updates or special offers. If you don’t want to receive such emails from us, you are free to unsubscribe from the mailing list.

#### Sharing Your Personal Information

We respect and protect your private information, and do not disclose it to anyone. We will share your Personal Information only in the following cases:

  * _Affiliates:_ In some cases we may closely cooperate with some companies and/or businesses, and your Personal Information may be required for various transactions with these partners.
  * _Agents:_ We may employ other companies to act as intermediate parties for us; therefore we may share our customers’ private information with them. These agents won’t use your information for purposes other than assisting us.
  * _Business Transfers:_ Customer information belongs to the Company’s business assets. Therefore when the Company becomes owned by a third party as the result of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or bankruptcy, customer information is passed to this third party as well.
  * _Protection of the Company and Others:_ If your Personal Information will be required by the government or legal institutions, we have the right to reveal it in order to comply with the law or protect our rights, property, employees, users etc.
  * _With Your Consent:_ You will be informed about other possible cases of sharing your Personal Information, and will have the right to prevent this.

#### Security

We do everything to secure private information of our customers by implementing the newest data protection technologies. However, we cannot ensure the 100% security of your Personal Information. Various system failures or unauthorized access may jeopardize user information at any time. If you navigate to some other websites from our website, please be aware that we are no longer responsible for privacy policies of other sites and services.

#### Changes To This Policy

We will keep you up to date about any possible changes to our Privacy Policy. As soon as such changes occur, we will inform you either via email or via our website.

#### Questions?

We are open to any questions on this Privacy Policy. Please address all your concerns to email.
